Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series II: Manuscripts
  - LaBombarda, Michael-Poets Don't Lose Gunfights with the Moon, undated (Box 15, Folder 100)
  - LaBombarda, Michael-Seascape and Other Poems, undated (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - LaBombarda, Michael-Watching Green Tomatoes Turn Red, undated (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Leary, Mary-Mss. Sent together to RK w/als: A Home of Their Own, West Coast Beach Strategies (in 3 parts), Dear Mother, Some Lesser-Known Facts About Our Friend the Potato, Class Act, two untitled poems, undated (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Litzky, Tsaurah-How I Got My Apartment, undated (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - Madore, Michael-Balls, undated (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Maynard, Joe-Our Hitlers, Our Selves (c. 1), undated (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - Maynard, Joe-Our Hitlers, Our Selves (c. 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - Moser, Raphael-untitled poems, undated (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - Nostrand, Jennifer-untitled poems, undated (Box 15, Folder 109)
  - Nufer, Doug-Fifty-two Pickup, undated (Box 15, Folder 110)
  - Nufer, Doug-On the Roast, undated (Box 15, Folder 111)
  - Nufer, Doug-Mss. Sent together to RK w/ als -Start Quoting Him Now -Restraining Order -Press Lace, undated (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - Ostashevsky, Eugene-Autobiography, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Ostashevsky, Eugene-Rome Rhyme: One Novissima Dicta Hecatombe De Vanitate Mundi, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Penn, John-Clear As A Bell, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Pintonelli, Deborah-Mia Wong, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Randall, Michael-Emily Dickenson Cut-Up w/ Charles Bukowski, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Randall, Michael-Our Bodies, Ourselves Cut-up w/ Hellfire, The Jerry Lee Lewis Story (c. 1), undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Randall, Michael-Our Bodies, Ourselves Cut-up w/ Hellfire, The Jerry Lee Lewis Story (c. 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Randall, Michael-Sexual Personae Cut-up w/ The Wild Boys, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Rappaport, Jill-Nyah Pah de Pamplemousses en Pennsylvania (A Modern Tale of Terror), undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Roberts, C. F.-Jezebel's Wig (A Caustic Lament), undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Rose, Joel-What Colt Did, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Savage, Tom-Last Heart Beat, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Savage, Tom-Poems, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Scutti, Susan-Economics, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Scutti, Susan-Insured, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Sparrow-The Boost, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Sparrow-untitled poem, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Sparrow-Today on Avenue C, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Sparrow-Prayers, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Sparrow-Bombs, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Sparrow-To S_______, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Sparrow-The Ram, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Sparrow-Independence Day, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Sparrow-A Directive, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Sparrow-I Bomb Because I Love, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Sparrow-Between Bombings, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Sparrow-Dollar, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Watson, Carl-Invitation to Insomnia, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Watson, Carl-Invitation to Insomnia (Tales from the Other Side of 90s New York), undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Weber, Bruce-Atget and the Sweeper, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Whitehead, Rollo-"New, Unpublished Rollo", undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Wierzbicki, Carol-Avon, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Witz, Bob-untitled poem, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Wortsman, Peter-Willy B. Weed: A Downtown Fairy Tale, undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series III: The Unbearables
  - Subseries A: The Unbearables
    - Miscellaneous Illustrations and Artwork, undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Art for Unbearables' first anthology, undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Furious Fictions, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Unbearable Smoot, April 1996 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Speed Reading #2, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Call for submissions to Unbearable Portfolio 3-theme: "Collaboration:, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - NYPress Piece by Sparrow, October 1997 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Announcement for Ghost Stories Reading (Japan), undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Piece on QuickCam by Dave Mandl (Village Voice, 1997) (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Lawrence Fishberg's First Person article "Surrealism;" reader letters on "Surrealism," Mike Topp and Jonathan Ames, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Materials for Assembling Magazine #6, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Unbearables at Alterknit, August 1997 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Alfred Vitale's "McDonald's McGrease," May 1997 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Materials from Reading in Boston, July 1997: "For Love and Money" (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Global Warming Issue of Unbearables Assembling Magazine (#7), undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Sharon Mesmer's 1997 Book Tour ("Chelsea Girl") (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Misc. For Robert Frost Issue of Big Fish, undated (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - The Unbearables Trash Self-Help Books cover art and flyer, undated (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Pamphlet for "Angelus Novus", undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Review of Sparrow's Republican Like Me (Village Voice 1997) (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Village Voice article re: Wm. S. Burroughs, 1997; Time Out/Voice Readings Announcements (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Materials for Fourth Annual Brooklyn Bridge Reading, undated (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Poem by Ron Kolm (One Stop), w/ graphics by Bob Witz, undated (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Graphic for "Artifacts Unlimited", undated (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Cover of Art in America Magazine w/ ad for "Notable Notes" on back, undated (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Audart Event (May 2, 1997)-Conway's (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Garden Gnome of Gethsemene, undated (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - S. F. Book Festival 1998 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Announcement for Gizzi & Mesmer Reading (BMA, 1998) (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Erotic Poetry for T-shirt, undated (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Unbearables Assembling Magazine #8 materials, undated (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Materials from Unbearables Reading in Philly (11/1/98), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Unbearables renovate "Rent", undated (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - The Cafe Review, Fall 1998-Unbearables Issue (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Ms. For Kolm and A. Kaufman's "Thunders Mouth Anthology"-sent to Cafe Review, undated (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Poetry Mss. For Unbearables Issue of Cafe Review, undated (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Merry Fortune bio and photo, undated (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Misc. Materials for Unbearables Issue of Cafe Review, undated (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Beachstock '99, undated (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Misc. Materials re: "The Source" at Film Forum (9/19/99) (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Materials re: "The 100 Least Important Events of the Last Millennium", undated (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Materials re: Fifth Brooklyn Bridge Reading (9/13/99), 1999 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Materials for Assembling Magazine #9: Y2K Millennium Pandemonium, undated (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Materials re: Unbearables New Year's Day Reading, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Unbearables Stations of the Cross event (4/2/99), 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Materials for Web Mag, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Materials in Beehive Journal (6/99), 1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Ms: Shalom-assembled poems: Tree, Wiggling Wish Boner, Parking, Fucker, Mined Art, No Day Like Today, My Ideal Clone, Residue/Dump, You and the Game, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Unbearables, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Surge Logo, N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - ABJ Poetry/Book Reading, N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Ms: Feast, Jim-Origins of The Proto Unbearables, N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - American Book Review article, "Bearing the Unbearables," N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Bil Bok Magazine, Vol. 6, N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Unbearables "ABR File," N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - List of Ron Kolm's videos, N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Flyer for The Unbearable Lighting of A Campfire, N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Unbearable Poetry Reading on the Brooklyn Bridge-flyer, N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - New Leaves Review 19, graphics and Mss., N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Subseries B: Crimes of the Beats
    - Invitation to Poetry Reading/Party in honor of Jack Kerouac, March 1989 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Letter re: Beats to Ron Kolm, April 1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Beats' Commentary on Ginsberg feature in NY Magazine, September 1994 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - New York Times article on Ginsberg, September 1994 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Vogue article on Beats, October 1995 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Beat Generation Catalog, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Christmas card from Jan Kerouac w/ photos, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Article on Jack Kerouac, London Review of Books, October 1995 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Letter and Ms. (Buddhagate at NYU) from Gerry Nicosia, November 1995 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Obituary for Jan Kerouac (NY Times National, March 1996); Jack Kerouac estate (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Rob Hardin Ms: "R.I.P., NAMBLA Enthusiast: A Scholarly Exchange", undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Cups Magazine w/ Allen Ginsberg Interview, June/July 1997 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Reading at Sacred Body Arts, 4/21/98, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Crimes of the Beats book review (Review of Contemporary Fiction), Fall 1998 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Crimes of the Beats cover graphic, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Beats Ms: Manners for the New Millennium, by Judy Nylon, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Beats Ms: Reflections on Beat Sexism, by Tsaurah Litzky, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Printout of early version of Crimes of the Beats, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Crimes of the Beats floppy disks (containing Mss.), undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Crimes of the Beats Manuscripts-collated, undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Page Proof of Crimes of the Beats, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Original Art for Crimes of the Beats, undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Mss. Not published in Beats, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Ms.: A. D. Winans-For Allen Ginsberg and Howl, undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Mss: Susan Sherman-Twelve in Transit; Berkeley, 1959 (excerpted from Amerika's Child, A Biohistory) (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Ms.: Lee Klein-Sitting on Corso's Poetry, undated (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Ms.: Mary Leary-On the Road with Frequent Rest Stops, undated (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Sparrow Mss. (untitled), N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Bob Witz Ms. (untitled), N.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Crimes of the Beats Miscellaneous, undated (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series IV: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists
    - Acker, Kathy, undated (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Allen, Roberta, undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Anthony, Bill, undated (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Barker, Molly, undated (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Benderson, Bruce, undated (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Bernard, Kenneth, undated (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Bernstein, Charles, undated (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Berrigan, Ted, undated (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Blagg, Max, undated (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Blowdryer, Jennifer, undated (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Brown, Ken, undated (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Burroughs, William S., undated (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Caesar, Ketan Ben, undated (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Cale, David, undated (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Carter, Michael, undated (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Cherches, Peter, undated (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Coleman, Joe, undated (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Delany, Samuel, undated (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Drooker, Eric, undated (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Dunn, Katherine, undated (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Ebersole, Lucinda, undated (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Eidus, Janice, undated (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Eighner, Lars, undated (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Finley, Karen, undated (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Flesh, Henry, undated (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - FLY, undated (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Freeman, Dan, undated (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Friedman, Drew, undated (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Friedman-August, Dorothy, undated (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Garret, George, undated (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Gangemi, Ken, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Golden, Mike, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Hardin, Rob, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Haring, Keith, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Holman, Bob, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Huberman, David, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Indiana, Gary, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Kasper, Michael, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Katchor, Ben, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Kaz, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Kerouac, Jack, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Kerouac, Jan, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Kruger, Barbara, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - LaPrade, Erik, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - LaTour, Jose, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Lewis, Marilyn Jane, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Lifshin, Lyn, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Linquist, Ona, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Litzky, Tsaurah, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Lupino, Stephan, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Mandl, David, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Manister, Diana, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Martin, Douglas, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Maynard, Joe, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - McGonigle, Thomas, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Mesmer, Sharon, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Minkowitz, Donna, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Mueller, Cookie, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Nersesian, Arthur, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Nostrand, Jennifer, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Nufer, Doug, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Nurske, Dennis, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - O'Brien, Geoffrey, undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Ostashevsky, Eugene, undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Padua, Jose, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Passaro, Vince, undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Peabody, Richard, undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Piazza, Tom, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Plantenga, Bart, undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Polonoff, David, undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Reith, Gerry, undated (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Rose, Joel, undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Rutkowski, Thaddeus, undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Sand, Catherine Rutgers, undated (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Sandlin, David, undated (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Savage, Tom, undated (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Saxon, Erik, undated (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Schneeman, Carolee, undated (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Siegle, Robert, undated (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Sirowitz, Hal, undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Sparrow, undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Speigelman, Art, undated (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Strausbaugh, John, undated (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Sukenick, Ronald, undated (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Tillman, Lynne, undated (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Tobocman, Seth, undated (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Topp, Mike, undated (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Torres, Edwin, undated (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Ulin, David, undated (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Watson, Carl, undated (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Weber, Bruce, undated (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Wierzbicki, Carol, undated (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Winter, Patricia, undated (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Wittig, Rob, undated (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Wood, Arthur, undated (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Wortsman, Peter, undated (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Author Misc., undated (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects
    - Appearances Magazine, undated (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Between C & D, undated (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Big Cigars Magazine, undated (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Bindlestiff Family Cirkus, undated (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Coney Island, USA, undated (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Digitas, undated (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Downtown writers and artists, undated (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - East Village scene, undated (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Eastern News Distributors, undated (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Evening of Romance, undated (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - The Fugs, undated (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Heretical Society, undated (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Low Tech Manual, undated (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Magazines, undated (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - New Observations, undated (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Outlaw Bible, undated (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Outlaw Poets' Reading, Oct. 22, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - PIM, undated (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Paper Tiger TV, undated (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Phun Phactory, undated (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Pink Pages, undated (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - PopSmear Magazine, undated (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Public Illumination Magazine, undated (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Rank Cologne, undated (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Rant, undated (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Raw, undated (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - Readings, undated (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - St. Mark's Bookshop, undated (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - Soft Skull Press, undated (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - Snake Eyes 2, undated (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - WFMU, undated (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - General Subject Misc., undated (Box 18, Folder 105)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series V: Photographs
  - Unbearables, by Lydia Tomkin, undated (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Kolm, Mesmer and Ackerman, undated (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Mary Leary, undated (Box 18, Folder 108)
  - Philly Reading 1998, by Bonny Finberg (Box 18, Folder 109)
  - Unbearables at Halloween party, by C. Wierzbicki, undated (Box 18, Folder 110)
  - Unbearables at Magazine Put-together party, by L. Tomkin, undated (Box 18, Folder 111)
  - Unbearables' Atlantic City trip, 7/24/99, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 112)
  - Unbearable Banquet at 'Ukranian National Home,' by Lydia Tomkin (10/22/99), 1999 (Box 18, Folder 113)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series VI: Announcements
  - Subseries A: Readings
    - 76 Varick, undated (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - ABC No Rio, undated (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - Angel Orensanz Foundation, undated (Box 18, Folder 116)
    - Angel's, undated (Box 18, Folder 117)
    - The Art Market, undated (Box 18, Folder 118)
    - Atticus Books and Music, undated (Box 18, Folder 119)
    - Audart, undated (Box 18, Folder 120)
    - Back Fence, undated (Box 18, Folder 121)
    - The Baggot Inn, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Barnes and Noble, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bellevue Art Museum, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Biblio's, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn Museum of Art, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - CBGB, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - CUNY, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Cafe Nico, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Cafe Fuerte, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Celeste Bartos Forum, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Cendrillon, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Ceres Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - The Charleston, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Civic Center Synagogue, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Chez LaRoe, undated (Box 1, Folder 23a.)
    - CLUB 86ed, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Columbia University, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Creation, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Crystalina's, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Dia Center for the Arts, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - A Different Light, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Dixon Place, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Don's Hill, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - The Drawing Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - E3 Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - The Ear Inn, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Eidia House West, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Fales Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - The Farm, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Gallery Stendhal, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - The Gershwin Hotel, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Globe Cafe, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Granary Books, undated (Box 1, Folder 40a.)
    - HERE, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - IN-Flux, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Jack Tilton Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - KGB, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Kinokuniya Bookstore, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Knitting Factory, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - La Mama La Galleria, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - The Lamb's Theater, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Le Gamin Chelsea, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Life, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - The Little Theater, undated (Box 1, Folder 50a.)
    - Mare Chiaro, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Marymount Manhattan College, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Medicine Show Theater, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Mendez Mural Garden, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Middle Collegiate Church Women's Guild, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - MIX, undated (Box 1, Folder 55a.)
    - Mr. Babbington's, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - The National Arts Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - National Design Museum, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - New School for Social Research, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - The News Room, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Opera, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Pace Wildenstein, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Phlebus Book Shop, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - The Phoenix Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - The Pink Pony, undated (Box 1, Folder 64a.)
    - The Poetry Project, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Poets and Writers, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Poet's House, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Poet's Theater, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Printed Matter, Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Puerto Rican Traveling Theater, undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Queer Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Rising Cafe, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Romanian Cultural Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Roulette, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Ruse, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - The Salon, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Savoy Lounge, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Segue Foundation Performance Space, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Serena, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Siberia, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Sixth and B Garden, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Small Press Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Sotheby's, undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Spacewurm, undated (Box 1, Folder 83a.)
    - The Speakeasy Cafe, undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Starve Theater, undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Stefan Stux Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Studio 17, undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Surf Reality's X-Tasy Salon, undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Tibor De Nagy Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Tonic, undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Tower Books, undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Tribes Gallery, undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Tricia Collins: Grand Salon, undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Video Lounge, undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Void, undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - WNYE, undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Way of Action Studio, undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - West Chelsea Arts Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - White Columns, undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Williamsburg Art and Historical Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Zinc Bar, undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements
    - 304 art, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)